<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE groups SYSTEM "groups.dtd" >
<groups>
    <group id="1">
      <name>name1</name>
      <description>(1) honeymoon, n.:
	A short period of doting between dating and debting.
		-- Ray C. Bandy</description>
    </group>

    <group id="2">
      <name>name2</name>
      <description>(2) Has anyone ever tasted an "end"?  Are they really bitter?</description>
    </group>

    <group id="3">
      <name>name3</name>
      <description>(3) Most people have a furious itch to talk about themselves and are restrained
only by the disinclination of others to listen.  Reserve is an artificial
quality that is developed in most of us as the result of innumerable rebuffs.
		-- W.S. Maugham</description>
    </group>

    <group id="4">
      <name>name4</name>
      <description>(4) If the future isn't what it used to be, does that
mean that the past is subject to change in times to come?</description>
    </group>

    <group id="5">
      <name>name5</name>
      <description>(5) Given my druthers, I'd druther not.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="6">
      <name>name6</name>
      <description>(6) Galbraith's Law of Human Nature:
	Faced with the choice between changing one's mind and proving that
there is no need to do so, almost everybody gets busy on the proof.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="7">
      <name>name7</name>
      <description>(7) Either I'm dead or my watch has stopped.
		-- Groucho Marx's last words</description>
    </group>

    <group id="8">
      <name>name8</name>
      <description>(8) Q:	Why do the police always travel in threes?
A:	One to do the reading, one to do the writing, and the other keeps
	an eye on the two intellectuals.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="9">
      <name>name9</name>
      <description>(9) "They're unfriendly, which is fortunate, really.  They'd be difficult
to like."
		-- Avon</description>
    </group>

    <group id="10">
      <name>name10</name>
      <description>(10) If you're like most homeowners, you're afraid that many repairs
around your home are too difficult to tackle.  So, when your furnace
explodes, you call in a so-called professional to fix it.  The
"professional" arrives in a truck with lettering on the sides and deposits a
large quantity of tools and two assistants who spend the better part of the
week in your basement whacking objects at random with heavy wrenches, after
which the "professional" returns and gives you a bill for slightly more
money than it would cost you to run a successful campaign for the U.S.
Senate.
	And that's why you've decided to start doing things yourself. You
figure, "If those guys can fix my furnace, then so can I.  How difficult can
it be?"
	Very difficult.  In fact, most home projects are impossible, which
is why you should do them yourself.  There is no point in paying other
people to screw things up when you can easily screw them up yourself for far
less money.  This article can help you.
		-- Dave Barry, "The Taming of the Screw"</description>
    </group>

    <group id="11">
      <name>name11</name>
      <description>(11) Please stand for the National Anthem:

	Australians all, let us rejoice,
	For we are young and free.
	We've golden soil and wealth for toil
	Our home is girt by sea.
	Our land abounds in nature's gifts
	Of beauty rich and rare.
	In history's page, let every stage
	Advance Australia Fair.
	In joyful strains then let us sing,
	Advance Australia Fair.

Thank you.  You may resume your seat.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="12">
      <name>name12</name>
      <description>(12) Being a mime means never having to say you're sorry.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="13">
      <name>name13</name>
      <description>(13) :SIG: /sig/ /n./  (also common as a prefix in combining forms)
   A Special Interest Group, in one of several technical areas,
   sponsored by the Association for Computing Machinery; well-known
   ones include SIGPLAN (the Special Interest Group on Programming
   Languages), SIGARCH (the Special Interest Group for Computer
   Architecture) and SIGGRAPH (the Special Interest Group for Computer
   Graphics).  Hackers, not surprisingly, like to overextend this
   naming convention to less formal associations like SIGBEER (at ACM
   conferences) and SIGFOOD (at University of Illinois).</description>
    </group>

    <group id="14">
      <name>name14</name>
      <description>(14) :furrfu: // /excl./  [Usenet] Written-only equivalent of
   "Sheesh!"; it is, in fact, "sheesh" modified by {rot13}.
   Evolved in mid-1992 as a response to notably silly postings
   repeating urban myths on the Usenet newsgroup
   alt.folklore.urban, after some posters complained that
   "Sheesh!" as a response to {newbie}s was being overused.  See
   also {FOAF}.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="15">
      <name>name15</name>
      <description>(15) Consider the postage stamp: its usefulness consists in the ability to
stick to one thing till it gets there.
		-- Josh Billings</description>
    </group>

    <group id="16">
      <name>name16</name>
      <description>(16) Anything that is good and useful is made of chocolate.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="17">
      <name>name17</name>
      <description>(17) We wish you a Hare Krishna
We wish you a Hare Krishna
We wish you a Hare Krishna
And a Sun Myung Moon!
		-- Maxwell Smart</description>
    </group>

    <group id="18">
      <name>name18</name>
      <description>(18) :mega-: /me'g*/ /pref./ [SI] See {{quantifiers}}.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="19">
      <name>name19</name>
      <description>(19) It is only people of small moral stature who have to stand on their
dignity.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="20">
      <name>name20</name>
      <description>(20) :peek: /n.,vt./  (and {poke}) The commands in most
   microcomputer BASICs for directly accessing memory contents at an
   absolute address; often extended to mean the corresponding
   constructs in any {HLL} (peek reads memory, poke modifies it).
   Much hacking on small, non-MMU micros consists of `peek'ing
   around memory, more or less at random, to find the location where
   the system keeps interesting stuff.  Long (and variably accurate)
   lists of such addresses for various computers circulate (see
   {{interrupt list, the}}).  The results of `poke's at these
   addresses may be highly useful, mildly amusing, useless but neat,
   or (most likely) total {lossage} (see {killer poke}).

   Since a {real operating system} provides useful, higher-level
   services for the tasks commonly performed with peeks and pokes on
   micros, and real languages tend not to encourage low-level memory
   groveling, a question like "How do I do a peek in C?" is
   diagnostic of the {newbie}.  (Of course, OS kernels often have to
   do exactly this; a real C hacker would unhesitatingly, if
   unportably, assign an absolute address to a pointer variable and
   indirect through it.)</description>
    </group>

    <group id="21">
      <name>name21</name>
      <description>(21) [Norm returns from the hospital.]

Coach:  What's up, Norm?
Norm:   Everything that's supposed to be.
		-- Cheers, Diane Meets Mom

Sam:  What's new, Normie?
Norm: Terrorists, Sam.  They've taken over my stomach.  They're demanding beer.
		-- Cheers, The Heart is a Lonely Snipehunter

Coach: What'll it be, Normie?
Norm:  Just the usual, Coach.  I'll have a froth of beer and a snorkel.
		-- Cheers, King of the Hill</description>
    </group>

    <group id="22">
      <name>name22</name>
      <description>(22) I just need enough to tide me over until I need more.
		-- Bill Hoest</description>
    </group>

    <group id="23">
      <name>name23</name>
      <description>(23) ___====-_  _-====___
	      _--~~~#####//      \\#####~~~--_
	   _-~##########// (    ) \\##########~-_
	  -############//  :\^^/:  \\############-
	_~############//   (@::@)   \\############~_
       ~#############((     \\//     ))#############~
      -###############\\    (^^)    //###############-
     -#################\\  / "" \  //#################-
    -###################\\/      \//###################-
   _#/:##########/\######(   /\   )######/\##########:\#_
   :/ :#/\#/\#/\/  \#/\##\  :  :  /##/\#/  \/\#/\#/\#: \:
   "  :/  V  V  "   V  \#\: :  : :/#/  V   "  V  V  \:  "
      "   "  "      "   \ : :  : : /   "      "  "   "</description>
    </group>

    <group id="24">
      <name>name24</name>
      <description>(24) Bore, n:
	A person who talks when you wish him to listen.
		-- Ambrose Bierce</description>
    </group>

    <group id="25">
      <name>name25</name>
      <description>(25) THE LESSER-KNOWN PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES #10: SIMPLE

SIMPLE is an acronym for Sheer Idiot's Monopurpose Programming Language
Environment.  This language, developed at the Hanover College for
Technological Misfits, was designed to make it impossible to write code
with errors in it.  The statements are, therefore, confined to BEGIN,
END and STOP.  No matter how you arrange the statements, you can't make
a syntax error.  Programs written in SIMPLE do nothing useful.  Thus
they achieve the results of programs written in other languages without
the tedious, frustrating process of testing and debugging.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="26">
      <name>name26</name>
      <description>(26) A friend of mine is into Voodoo Acupuncture.  You don't have to go.
You'll just be walking down the street and...  Ooohh, that's much better.
		-- Steven Wright</description>
    </group>

    <group id="27">
      <name>name27</name>
      <description>(27) You know it's going to be a long day when you get up, shave and shower,
start to get dressed and your shoes are still warm.
		-- Dean Webber</description>
    </group>

    <group id="28">
      <name>name28</name>
      <description>(28) Come live with me, and be my love,
And we will some new pleasures prove
Of golden sands, and crystal brooks,
With silken lines, and silver hooks.
		-- John Donne</description>
    </group>

    <group id="29">
      <name>name29</name>
      <description>(29) Mistrust first impulses; they are always right.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="30">
      <name>name30</name>
      <description>(30) Nothing succeeds like the appearance of success.
		-- Christopher Lascl</description>
    </group>

    <group id="31">
      <name>name31</name>
      <description>(31) Do your part to help preserve life on Earth -- by trying to preserve your own.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="32">
      <name>name32</name>
      <description>(32) :kremvax: /krem-vaks/ /n./  [from the then large number of
   {Usenet} {VAXen} with names of the form foovax]
   Originally, a fictitious Usenet site at the Kremlin, announced on
   April 1, 1984 in a posting ostensibly originated there by Soviet
   leader Konstantin Chernenko.  The posting was actually forged by
   Piet Beertema as an April Fool's joke.  Other fictitious sites
   mentioned in the hoax were moskvax and {kgbvax}.  This was
   probably the funniest of the many April Fool's forgeries
   perpetrated on Usenet (which has negligible security against them),
   because the notion that Usenet might ever penetrate the Iron
   Curtain seemed so totally absurd at the time.

   In fact, it was only six years later that the first genuine site in
   Moscow, demos.su, joined Usenet.  Some readers needed
   convincing that the postings from it weren't just another prank.
   Vadim Antonov, senior programmer at Demos and the major poster from
   there up to mid-1991, was quite aware of all this, referred to it
   frequently in his own postings, and at one point twitted some
   credulous readers by blandly asserting that he *was* a
   hoax!

   Eventually he even arranged to have the domain's gateway site
   named kremvax, thus neatly turning fiction into fact
   and demonstrating that the hackish sense of humor transcends
   cultural barriers.  [Mr. Antonov also contributed the
   Russian-language material for this lexicon. --ESR]

   In an even more ironic historical footnote, kremvax became an
   electronic center of the anti-communist resistance during the
   bungled hard-line coup of August 1991.  During those three days the
   Soviet UUCP network centered on kremvax became the only
   trustworthy news source for many places within the USSR.  Though
   the sysops were concentrating on internal communications,
   cross-border postings included immediate transliterations of Boris
   Yeltsin's decrees condemning the coup and eyewitness reports of the
   demonstrations in Moscow's streets.  In those hours, years of
   speculation that totalitarianism would prove unable to maintain its
   grip on politically-loaded information in the age of computer
   networking were proved devastatingly accurate -- and the original
   kremvax joke became a reality as Yeltsin and the new Russian
   revolutionaries of `glasnost' and `perestroika' made
   kremvax one of the timeliest means of their outreach to the
   West.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="33">
      <name>name33</name>
      <description>(33) Stuckness shouldn't be avoided.  It's the psychic predecessor of all
real understanding.  An egoless acceptance of stuckness is a key to an
understanding of all Quality, in mechanical work as in other endeavors.
		-- R. Pirsig, "Zen and the Art of Motorcycle Maintenance"</description>
    </group>

    <group id="34">
      <name>name34</name>
      <description>(34) The one charm of marriage is that it makes a life of deception a neccessity.
		-- Oscar Wilde</description>
    </group>

    <group id="35">
      <name>name35</name>
      <description>(35) Nothing endures but change.
		-- Heraclitus
	[Yeah, yeah, "Everything changes but change itself." --JFK Ed.]</description>
    </group>

    <group id="36">
      <name>name36</name>
      <description>(36) Once, there was NO fun ... This was before MENU planning, FASHION
statements or NAUTILUS equipment ... Then, in 1985 ... FUN was
completely encoded in this tiny MICROCHIP ... It contain 14,768 vaguely
amusing SIT-COM pilots!!  We had to wait FOUR BILLION years but we
finally got JERRY LEWIS, MTV and a large selection of creme-filled
snack cakes!</description>
    </group>

    <group id="37">
      <name>name37</name>
      <description>(37) Necessity is a mother.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="38">
      <name>name38</name>
      <description>(38) Ask your boss to reconsider -- it's so difficult to take "Go to hell"
for an answer.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="39">
      <name>name39</name>
      <description>(39) Economies of scale:
	The notion that bigger is better.  In particular, that if you want
	a certain amount of computer power, it is much better to buy one
	biggie than a bunch of smallies.  Accepted as an article of faith
	by people who love big machines and all that complexity.  Rejected
	as an article of faith by those who love small machines and all
	those limitations.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="40">
      <name>name40</name>
      <description>(40) A lie is an abomination unto the Lord and a very present help in time of
trouble.
		-- Adlai Stevenson</description>
    </group>

    <group id="41">
      <name>name41</name>
      <description>(41) :perfect programmer syndrome: /n./  Arrogance; the egotistical
   conviction that one is above normal human error.  Most frequently
   found among programmers of some native ability but relatively
   little experience (especially new graduates; their perceptions may
   be distorted by a history of excellent performance at solving
   {toy problem}s).  "Of course my program is correct, there is no
   need to test it."  "Yes, I can see there may be a problem here,
   but *I'll* never type `rm -r /' while in {root
   mode}."</description>
    </group>

    <group id="42">
      <name>name42</name>
      <description>(42) San Francisco isn't what it used to be, and it never was.
		-- Herb Caen</description>
    </group>

    <group id="43">
      <name>name43</name>
      <description>(43) Genius is pain.
		-- John Lennon</description>
    </group>

    <group id="44">
      <name>name44</name>
      <description>(44) algorithm, n.:
	Trendy dance for hip programmers.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="45">
      <name>name45</name>
      <description>(45) While having never invented a sin, I'm trying to perfect several.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="46">
      <name>name46</name>
      <description>(46) We were so poor we couldn't afford a watchdog.
If we heard a noise at night, we'd bark ourselves.
		-- Crazy Jimmy</description>
    </group>

    <group id="47">
      <name>name47</name>
      <description>(47) Did you ever wonder what you'd say to God if He sneezed?</description>
    </group>

    <group id="48">
      <name>name48</name>
      <description>(48) You now have Asian Flu.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="49">
      <name>name49</name>
      <description>(49) QOTD:
	"Oh, no, no...  I'm not beautiful.  Just very, very pretty."</description>
    </group>

    <group id="50">
      <name>name50</name>
      <description>(50) Majority, n.:
	That quality that distinguishes a crime from a law.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="51">
      <name>name51</name>
      <description>(51) Nowlan's Theory:
	He who hesitates is not only lost, but several miles from
	the next freeway exit.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="52">
      <name>name52</name>
      <description>(52) A doctoral student from Buckingham
Wrote his thesis on cunts and on fucking'em.
	But a dropout from paree
	Taught him Gamahuchee
So he added a footnote on sucking 'em.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="53">
      <name>name53</name>
      <description>(53) :ELIZA effect: /*-li:'z* *-fekt'/ /n./  [AI community] The
   tendency of humans to attach associations to terms from prior
   experience.  For example, there is nothing magic about the symbol
   `+' that makes it well-suited to indicate addition; it's just
   that people associate it with addition.  Using `+' or `plus'
   to mean addition in a computer language is taking advantage of the
   ELIZA effect.

   This term comes from the famous ELIZA program by Joseph Weizenbaum,
   which simulated a Rogerian psychotherapist by rephrasing many of
   the patient's statements as questions and posing them to the
   patient.  It worked by simple pattern recognition and substitution
   of key words into canned phrases.  It was so convincing, however,
   that there are many anecdotes about people becoming very
   emotionally caught up in dealing with ELIZA.  All this was due to
   people's tendency to attach to words meanings which the computer
   never put there.  The ELIZA effect is a {Good Thing} when
   writing a programming language, but it can blind you to serious
   shortcomings when analyzing an Artificial Intelligence system.
   Compare {ad-hockery}; see also {AI-complete}.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="54">
      <name>name54</name>
      <description>(54) The objective of all dedicated employees should be to thoroughly analyze
all situations, anticipate all problems prior to their occurrence, have
answers for these problems, and move swiftly to solve these problems
when called upon.
	However...
When you are up to your ass in alligators it is difficult to remind
yourself your initial objective was to drain the swamp.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="55">
      <name>name55</name>
      <description>(55) Gordon's first law:
	If a research project is not worth doing, it is not worth doing
well.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="56">
      <name>name56</name>
      <description>(56) Don't steal... the IRS hates competition!</description>
    </group>

    <group id="57">
      <name>name57</name>
      <description>(57) That that is is that that is not is not.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="58">
      <name>name58</name>
      <description>(58) *** System shutdown message from root ***

System going down in 60 seconds</description>
    </group>

    <group id="59">
      <name>name59</name>
      <description>(59) Remove me from this land of slaves,
Where all are fools, and all are knaves,
Where every knave and fool is bought, 
Yet kindly sells himself for nought;
		-- Jonathan Swift</description>
    </group>

    <group id="60">
      <name>name60</name>
      <description>(60) :clone: /n./  1. An exact duplicate: "Our product is a clone of
   their product."  Implies a legal reimplementation from
   documentation or by reverse-engineering.  Also connotes lower
   price.  2. A shoddy, spurious copy: "Their product is a clone of
   our product."  3. A blatant ripoff, most likely violating
   copyright, patent, or trade secret protections: "Your product is a
   clone of my product."  This use implies legal action is pending.
   4. `PC clone:' a PC-BUS/ISA or EISA-compatible 80x86-based
   microcomputer (this use is sometimes spelled `klone' or
   `PClone').  These invariably have much more bang for the buck
   than the IBM archetypes they resemble.  5. In the construction
   `Unix clone': An OS designed to deliver a Unix-lookalike
   environment without Unix license fees, or with additional
   `mission-critical' features such as support for real-time
   programming.  6. /v./ To make an exact copy of something.  "Let me
   clone that" might mean "I want to borrow that paper so I can make
   a photocopy" or "Let me get a copy of that file before you
   {mung} it".</description>
    </group>

    <group id="61">
      <name>name61</name>
      <description>(61) :off the trolley: /adj./  Describes the behavior of a program
   that malfunctions and goes catatonic, but doesn't actually
   {crash} or abort.  See {glitch}, {bug}, {deep space}.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="62">
      <name>name62</name>
      <description>(62) I use technology in order to hate it more properly.
		-- Nam June Paik</description>
    </group>

    <group id="63">
      <name>name63</name>
      <description>(63) "Well, that was a piece of cake, eh K-9?"

"Piece of cake, Master?  Radial slice of baked confection ... coefficient of
relevance to Key of Time: zero."
		-- Dr. Who</description>
    </group>

    <group id="64">
      <name>name64</name>
      <description>(64) It is better for civilization to be going down the drain than to be
coming up it.
		-- Henry Allen</description>
    </group>

    <group id="65">
      <name>name65</name>
      <description>(65) Where do I find the time for not reading so many books?
		-- Karl Kraus</description>
    </group>

    <group id="66">
      <name>name66</name>
      <description>(66) Let's organize this thing and take all the fun out of it.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="67">
      <name>name67</name>
      <description>(67) If you put tomfoolery into a computer, nothing comes out but tomfoolery.
But this tomfoolery, having passed through a very expensive machine,
is somehow enobled and no-one dare criticise it.
		-- Pierre Gallois</description>
    </group>

    <group id="68">
      <name>name68</name>
      <description>(68) I met my latest girl friend in a department store.  She was looking at
clothes, and I was putting Slinkys on the escalators.
		-- Steven Wright</description>
    </group>

    <group id="69">
      <name>name69</name>
      <description>(69) There was a young lady who said,
As her bridegroom got into the bed,
	"I'm tired of this stunt,
	That they do with one's cunt,
You can get up my bottom instead."</description>
    </group>

    <group id="70">
      <name>name70</name>
      <description>(70) When a woman gives me a present I have always two surprises:
first is the present, and afterward, having to pay for it.
		-- Donnay</description>
    </group>

    <group id="71">
      <name>name71</name>
      <description>(71) Recession is when your neighbor loses his job. Depression is when you
lose your job.  These economic downturns are very difficult to predict,
but sophisticated econometric modeling houses like Data Resources and
Chase Econometrics have successfully predicted 14 of the last 3 recessions.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="72">
      <name>name72</name>
      <description>(72) Never have children, only grandchildren.
		-- Gore Vidal</description>
    </group>

    <group id="73">
      <name>name73</name>
      <description>(73) You should make a point of trying every experience once -- except
incest and folk-dancing.
		-- A. Bax, "Farewell My Youth"</description>
    </group>

    <group id="74">
      <name>name74</name>
      <description>(74) There is no fear in love; but perfect love casteth out fear.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="75">
      <name>name75</name>
      <description>(75) Life is a serious burden, which no thinking, humane person would
wantonly inflict on someone else.
		-- Clarence Darrow</description>
    </group>

    <group id="76">
      <name>name76</name>
      <description>(76) I shall come to you in the night and we shall see who is stronger --
a little girl who won't eat her dinner or a great big man with cocaine
in his veins.
		-- Sigmund Freud, in a letter to his fiancee</description>
    </group>

    <group id="77">
      <name>name77</name>
      <description>(77) Climate and Surgery
	R C Gilchrist, who was shot by J Sharp twelve days ago, and who
received a derringer ball in the right breast, and who it was supposed at
the time could not live many hours, was on the street yesterday and the
day before -- walking several blocks at a time.  To those who design to be
riddled with bullets or cut to pieces with Bowie-knives, we cordially
recommend our Sacramento climate and Sacramento surgery.
		-- Sacramento Daily Union, September 11, 1861</description>
    </group>

    <group id="78">
      <name>name78</name>
      <description>(78) What they say:			What they mean:

New				Different colors from previous version.
All New				Not compatible with previous version.
Exclusive			Nobody else has documentation.
Unmatched			Almost as good as the competition.
Design Simplicity		The company wouldn't give us any money.
Fool-proof Operation		All parameters are hard-coded.
Advanced Design			Nobody really understands it.
Here At Last			Didn't get it done on time.
Field Tested			We don't have any simulators.
Years of Development		Finally got one to work.
Unprecedented Performance	Nothing ever ran this slow before.
Revolutionary			Disk drives go 'round and 'round.
Futuristic			Only runs on a next generation supercomputer.
No Maintenance			Impossible to fix.
Performance Proven		Worked through Beta test.
Meets Tough Quality Standards	It compiles without errors.
Satisfaction Guaranteed		We'll send you another pack if it fails.
Stock Item			We shipped it before and can do it again.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="79">
      <name>name79</name>
      <description>(79) When you're not looking at it, this fortune is written in FORTRAN.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="80">
      <name>name80</name>
      <description>(80) Al didn't smile for forty years.  You've got to admire a man like that.
		-- from "Mary Hartman, Mary Hartman"</description>
    </group>

    <group id="81">
      <name>name81</name>
      <description>(81) Bing's Rule:
	Don't try to stem the tide -- move the beach.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="82">
      <name>name82</name>
      <description>(82) Life is a gamble at terrible odds, if it was a bet you wouldn't take it.
		-- Tom Stoppard, "Rosencrantz and Guildenstern are Dead"</description>
    </group>

    <group id="83">
      <name>name83</name>
      <description>(83) Q:	How many marketing people does it take to change a lightbulb?
A:	I'll have to get back to you on that.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="84">
      <name>name84</name>
      <description>(84) :crash and burn: /vi.,n./  A spectacular crash, in the mode of
   the conclusion of the car-chase scene in the movie "Bullitt"
   and many subsequent imitators (compare {die horribly}).  Sun-3
   monitors losing the flyback transformer and lightning strikes on
   VAX-11/780 backplanes are notable crash and burn generators.  The
   construction `crash-and-burn machine' is reported for a computer
   used exclusively for alpha or {beta} testing, or reproducing
   bugs (i.e., not for development).  The implication is that it
   wouldn't be such a disaster if that machine crashed, since only the
   testers would be inconvenienced.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="85">
      <name>name85</name>
      <description>(85) Psychology.  Mind over matter.
Mind under matter?  It doesn't matter.
Never mind.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="86">
      <name>name86</name>
      <description>(86) :scream and die: /v./  Syn. {cough and die}, but connotes
   that an error message was printed or displayed before the program
   crashed.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="87">
      <name>name87</name>
      <description>(87) Qvid me anxivs svm?</description>
    </group>

    <group id="88">
      <name>name88</name>
      <description>(88) You k'n hide de fier, but w'at you gwine do wid de smoke?
		-- Joel Chandler Harris, proverbs of Uncle Remus</description>
    </group>

    <group id="89">
      <name>name89</name>
      <description>(89) Real computer scientists don't write code.  They occasionally tinker with
`programming systems', but those are so high level that they hardly count 
(and rarely count accurately; precision is for applications).</description>
    </group>

    <group id="90">
      <name>name90</name>
      <description>(90) He that composes himself is wiser than he that composes a book.
		-- B. Franklin</description>
    </group>

    <group id="91">
      <name>name91</name>
      <description>(91) The decision doesn't have to be logical; it was unanimous.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="92">
      <name>name92</name>
      <description>(92) If I'm over the hill, why is it I don't recall ever being on top?
		-- Jerry Muscha</description>
    </group>

    <group id="93">
      <name>name93</name>
      <description>(93) An Argentine gaucho named Bruno
Who said, "Fucking is one thing I do know.
	Women are fine
	And sheep are divine
But llamas are numero uno."</description>
    </group>

    <group id="94">
      <name>name94</name>
      <description>(94) I poured spot remover on my dog.  Now he's gone.
		-- Steven Wright</description>
    </group>

    <group id="95">
      <name>name95</name>
      <description>(95) mathematician, n.:
	Some one who believes imaginary things appear right before your _i's.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="96">
      <name>name96</name>
      <description>(96) You can't cheat the phone company.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="97">
      <name>name97</name>
      <description>(97) Stop searching forever.  Happiness is unattainable.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="98">
      <name>name98</name>
      <description>(98) Scott's second Law:
	When an error has been detected and corrected, it will be found
to have been wrong in the first place.

Corollary:
	After the correction has been found in error, it will be
impossible to fit the original quantity back into the equation.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="99">
      <name>name99</name>
      <description>(99) Do you think that illiterate people get the full effect of alphabet soup?</description>
    </group>

    <group id="100">
      <name>name100</name>
      <description>(100) I met my latest girl friend in a department store.  She was looking at
clothes, and I was putting Slinkys on the escalators.
		-- Steven Wright</description>
    </group>

</groups>

