<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE groups SYSTEM "groups.dtd" >
<groups>
    <group id="1">
      <name>name1</name>
      <description>(1) A good question is never answered.  It is not a bolt to be tightened
into place but a seed to be planted and to bear more seed toward the
hope of greening the landscape of idea.
		-- John Ciardi</description>
    </group>

    <group id="2">
      <name>name2</name>
      <description>(2) System/3!  System/3!
See how it runs! See how it runs!
	Its monitor loses so totally!
	It runs all its programs in RPG!
	It's made by our favorite monopoly!
System/3!</description>
    </group>

    <group id="3">
      <name>name3</name>
      <description>(3) Do what comes naturally.  Seethe and fume and throw a tantrum.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="4">
      <name>name4</name>
      <description>(4) There was a young lady at sea
Who said, "God, how it hurts me to pee."
	"I see," said the mate,
	"That accounts for the state
Of the captain, the purser, and me."</description>
    </group>

    <group id="5">
      <name>name5</name>
      <description>(5) The clergy successfully preached the doctrines of patience and pusillanimity;
the active virtues of society were discouraged; and the last remains of a
military spirit were buried in the cloister: a large portion of public and
private wealth was consecrated to the specious demands of charity and devotion;
and the soldiers' pay was lavished on the useless multitudes of both sexes
who could only plead the merits of abstinence and chastity.
		-- Edward Gibbons, "The Decline and Fall of the Roman Empire"</description>
    </group>

    <group id="6">
      <name>name6</name>
      <description>(6) "Terence, this is stupid stuff:
You eat your victuals fast enough;
There can't be much amiss, 'tis clear,
To see the rate you drink your beer.
But oh, good Lord, the verse you make,
It gives a chap the belly-ache.
The cow, the old cow, she is dead;
It sleeps well the horned head:
We poor lads, 'tis our turn now
To hear such tunes as killed the cow.
Pretty friendship 'tis to rhyme
Your friends to death before their time.
Moping, melancholy mad:
Come, pipe a tune to dance to, lad."
		-- A. E. Housman</description>
    </group>

    <group id="7">
      <name>name7</name>
      <description>(7) What if nothing exists and we're all in somebody's dream?  Or what's
worse, what if only that fat guy in the third row exists?
		-- Woody Allen, "Without Feathers"</description>
    </group>

    <group id="8">
      <name>name8</name>
      <description>(8) Alone, adj.:
	In bad company.
		-- Ambrose Bierce, "The Devil's Dictionary"</description>
    </group>

    <group id="9">
      <name>name9</name>
      <description>(9) Review Questions

1:	If Nerd on the planet Nutley starts out in his spaceship at 20 KPH,
	and his speed doubles every 3.2 seconds, how long will it be before
	he exceeds the speed of light?  How long will it be before the
	Galactic Patrol picks up the pieces of his spaceship?

2:	If Roger Rowdy wrecks his car every week, and each week he breaks
	twice as many bones as before, how long will it be before he breaks
	every bone in his body?  How long will it be before they cut off
	his insurance?  Where does he get a new car every week?

3:	If Johnson drinks one beer the first hour (slow start), four beers
	the next hour, nine beers the next, etc., and stacks the cans in
	a pyramid, how soon will Johnson's pyramid be larger than King
	Tut's?  When will it fall on him?  Will he notice?</description>
    </group>

    <group id="10">
      <name>name10</name>
      <description>(10) Alexander Graham Bell is alive and well
in New York, and still waiting for a dial tone.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="11">
      <name>name11</name>
      <description>(11) You've been telling me to relax all the way here,
and now you're telling me just to be myself?
		-- The Return of the Secaucus Seven</description>
    </group>

    <group id="12">
      <name>name12</name>
      <description>(12) The bank called to tell me that I'm overdrawn,
Some freaks are burning crosses out on my front lawn,
And I *can't*believe* it, all the Cheetos are gone,
	It's just ONE OF THOSE DAYS!
		-- Weird Al Yankovic, "One of Those Days"</description>
    </group>

    <group id="13">
      <name>name13</name>
      <description>(13) If God had a beard, he'd be a UNIX programmer.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="14">
      <name>name14</name>
      <description>(14) If I could drop dead right now, I'd be the happiest man alive!
		-- Samuel Goldwyn</description>
    </group>

    <group id="15">
      <name>name15</name>
      <description>(15) It is practically impossible to teach good programming to students that
have had a prior exposure to BASIC: as potential programmers they are
mentally mutilated beyond hope of regeneration.
		-- Edsger W. Dijkstra, SIGPLAN Notices, Volume 17, Number 5</description>
    </group>

    <group id="16">
      <name>name16</name>
      <description>(16) The devil can cite Scripture for his purpose.
		-- William Shakespeare, "The Merchant of Venice"</description>
    </group>

    <group id="17">
      <name>name17</name>
      <description>(17) Do not try to solve all life's problems at once -- learn to dread each
day as it comes.
		-- Donald Kaul</description>
    </group>

    <group id="18">
      <name>name18</name>
      <description>(18) Yes, but which self do you want to be?</description>
    </group>

    <group id="19">
      <name>name19</name>
      <description>(19) Science is built up of facts, as a house is with stones.  But a
collection of facts is no more a science than a heap of stones
is a house.
		-- Jules Henri Poincare</description>
    </group>

    <group id="20">
      <name>name20</name>
      <description>(20) I appoint you ambassador to Fantasy Island!!!</description>
    </group>

    <group id="21">
      <name>name21</name>
      <description>(21) Es brilig war.  Die schlichte Toven
	Wirrten und wimmelten in Waben;
Und aller-m"umsige Burggoven
	Dir mohmen R"ath ausgraben.
		-- Lewis Carrol, "Through the Looking Glass"</description>
    </group>

    <group id="22">
      <name>name22</name>
      <description>(22) There are no data that cannot be plotted on a straight line if the axis
are chosen correctly.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="23">
      <name>name23</name>
      <description>(23) We are all born mad.  Some remain so.
		-- Samuel Beckett</description>
    </group>

    <group id="24">
      <name>name24</name>
      <description>(24) The Road goes ever on and on
Down from the door where it began.
Now far ahead the Road has gone,
And I must follow, if I can,
Pursuing it with eager feet,
Until it joins some larger way
Where many paths and errands meet.
And whither then?  I cannot say.
		-- J. R. R. Tolkien</description>
    </group>

    <group id="25">
      <name>name25</name>
      <description>(25) Today when a man gets married he gets a home, a housekeeper, a cook, a
cheering squad and another paycheck.  When a woman marries, she gets a
boarder.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="26">
      <name>name26</name>
      <description>(26) :has the X nature:  [seems to derive from Zen Buddhist koans
   of the form "Does an X have the Buddha-nature?"] /adj./ Common
   hacker construction for `is an X', used for humorous emphasis.
   "Anyone who can't even use a program with on-screen help embedded
   in it truly has the {loser} nature!"  See also {the X that
   can be Y is not the true X}.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="27">
      <name>name27</name>
      <description>(27) A mother takes twenty years to make a man of her boy, and another woman
makes a fool of him in twenty minutes.
		-- Frost</description>
    </group>

    <group id="28">
      <name>name28</name>
      <description>(28) Darling: the popular form of address used in speaking to a member of the
opposite sex whose name you cannot at the moment remember.
		-- Oliver Herford</description>
    </group>

    <group id="29">
      <name>name29</name>
      <description>(29) George Orwell was an optimist.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="30">
      <name>name30</name>
      <description>(30) Humor in the Court:
Q.  And who is this person you are speaking of?
A.  My ex-widow said it.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="31">
      <name>name31</name>
      <description>(31) When Boy Scouts do it, it's intense.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="32">
      <name>name32</name>
      <description>(32) I will not play at tug o' war.
I'd rather play at hug o' war,
Where everyone hugs
Instead of tugs,
Where everyone giggles
And rolls on the rug,
Where everyone kisses,
And everyone grins,
And everyone cuddles,
And everyone wins.
		-- Shel Silverstein, "Hug o' War"</description>
    </group>

    <group id="33">
      <name>name33</name>
      <description>(33) In Boston, it is illegal to hold frog-jumping contests in nightclubs.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="34">
      <name>name34</name>
      <description>(34) Vegeterians beware!  You are what you eat.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="35">
      <name>name35</name>
      <description>(35) Actresses will happen in the best regulated families.
		-- Addison Mizner and Oliver Herford, "The Entirely
		New Cynic's Calendar", 1905</description>
    </group>

    <group id="36">
      <name>name36</name>
      <description>(36) :copious free time: /n./  [Apple; orig. fr. the intro to Tom
   Lehrer's song "It Makes A Fellow Proud To Be A Soldier"]
   1. [used ironically to indicate the speaker's lack of the quantity
   in question] A mythical schedule slot for accomplishing tasks held
   to be unlikely or impossible.  Sometimes used to indicate that the
   speaker is interested in accomplishing the task, but believes that
   the opportunity will not arise.  "I'll implement the automatic
   layout stuff in my copious free time."  2. [Archly] Time reserved
   for bogus or otherwise idiotic tasks, such as implementation of
   {chrome}, or the stroking of {suit}s.  "I'll get back to him
   on that feature in my copious free time."</description>
    </group>

    <group id="37">
      <name>name37</name>
      <description>(37) Never argue with a fool -- people might not be able to tell the difference.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="38">
      <name>name38</name>
      <description>(38) FORTUNE EXPLAINS WHAT JOB REVIEW CATCH PHRASES MEAN:	#4
consistent:
	Reviewee hasn't gotten anything right yet, and it is anticipated
	that this pattern will continue throughout the coming year.

an excellent sounding board:
	Present reviewee with any number of alternatives, and implement
	them in the order precisely opposite of his/her specification.

a planner and organizer:
	Usually manages to put on socks before shoes.  Can match the
	animal tags on his clothing.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="39">
      <name>name39</name>
      <description>(39) You are deeply attached to your friends and acquaintances.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="40">
      <name>name40</name>
      <description>(40) You have an unusual understanding of
the problems of human relationships.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="41">
      <name>name41</name>
      <description>(41) The Junior God now heads the roll
In the list of heaven's peers;
He sits in the House of High Control,
And he regulates the spheres.
Yet does he wonder, do you suppose,
If, even in gods divine,
The best and wisest may not be those
Who have wallowed awhile with the swine?
		-- R.W. Service</description>
    </group>

    <group id="42">
      <name>name42</name>
      <description>(42) Pittsburgh driver's test

(5) Your car's horn is a vital piece of safety equipment.  How often should
you test it?

	(a) once a year.
	(b) once a month.
	(c) once a day.
	(d) once an hour.

The correct answer is (d). You should test your car's horn at least once
every hour, and more often at night or in residential neighborhoods.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="43">
      <name>name43</name>
      <description>(43) QOTD:
	"The elder gods went to Suggoth and all I got was this lousy T-shirt."</description>
    </group>

    <group id="44">
      <name>name44</name>
      <description>(44) The past always looks better than it was.
It's only pleasant because it isn't here.
		-- Finley Peter Dunne (Mr. Dooley)</description>
    </group>

    <group id="45">
      <name>name45</name>
      <description>(45) Evil is that which one believes of others.  It is a sin to believe evil
of others, but it is seldom a mistake.
		-- H.L. Mencken</description>
    </group>

    <group id="46">
      <name>name46</name>
      <description>(46) Evil is that which one believes of others.  It is a sin to believe evil
of others, but it is seldom a mistake.
		-- H.L. Mencken</description>
    </group>

    <group id="47">
      <name>name47</name>
      <description>(47) One toke over the line, sweet Mary,
One toke over the line,
Sittin' downtown in a railway station,
One toke over the line.
Waitin' for the train that goes home,
Hopin' that the train is on time,
Sittin' downtown in a railway station,
One toke over the line.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="48">
      <name>name48</name>
      <description>(48) A woman without a man is like a fish without a bicycle.
Therefore, a man without a woman is like a bicycle without a fish.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="49">
      <name>name49</name>
      <description>(49) Sixtus V, Pope from 1585 to 1590 authorized a printing of the Vulgate
Bible.  Taking no chances, the pope issued a papal bull automatically
excommunicating any printer who might make an alteration in the text.
This he ordered printed at the beginning of the Bible.  He personally
examined every sheet as it came off the press.  Yet the published
Vulgate Bible contained so many errors that corrected scraps had to be
printed and pasted over them in every copy.  The result provoked wry
comments on the rather patchy papal infallibility, and Pope Sixtus had
no recourse but to order the return and destruction of every copy.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="50">
      <name>name50</name>
      <description>(50) "Now the Lord God planted a garden East of Whittier in a place called
Yorba Linda, and out of the ground he made to grow orange trees that
were good for food and the fruits thereof he labeled SUNKIST ..."
		-- "The Begatting of a President"</description>
    </group>

    <group id="51">
      <name>name51</name>
      <description>(51) You need only reflect that one of the best ways to get yourself a
reputation as a dangerous citizen these days is to go about repeating
the very phrases which our founding fathers used in the struggle for
independence.
		-- Charles A. Beard</description>
    </group>

    <group id="52">
      <name>name52</name>
      <description>(52) We're mortal -- which is to say, we're ignorant, stupid, and sinful --
but those are only handicaps.  Our pride is that nevertheless, now and
then, we do our best.  A few times we succeed.  What more dare we ask for?
		-- Ensign Flandry</description>
    </group>

    <group id="53">
      <name>name53</name>
      <description>(53) Psychoanalysis is that mental illness for which it regards itself
a therapy.
		-- Karl Kraus

Psychiatry is the care of the id by the odd.

Show me a sane man and I will cure him for you.
		-- C.G. Jung</description>
    </group>

    <group id="54">
      <name>name54</name>
      <description>(54) Heavy, adj.:
	Seduced by the chocolate side of the force.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="55">
      <name>name55</name>
      <description>(55) The Fastest Defeat In Chess
	The big name for us in the world of chess is Gibaud, a French chess
master.  
	In Paris during 1924 he was beaten after only four moves by a
Monsieur Lazard.  Happily for posterity, the moves are recorded and so
chess enthusiasts may reconstruct this magnificent collapse in the comfort
of their own homes.
	Lazard was black and Gibaud white:
	1: P-Q4, Kt-KB3
	2: Kt-Q2, P-K4
	3: PxP, Kt-Kt5
	4: P-K6, Kt-K6
	White then resigns on realizing that a fifth move would involve
either a Q-KR5 check or the loss of his queen.
		-- Stephen Pile, "The Book of Heroic Failures"</description>
    </group>

    <group id="56">
      <name>name56</name>
      <description>(56) A person who has both feet planted firmly
in the air can be safely called a liberal.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="57">
      <name>name57</name>
      <description>(57) I could dance with you till the cows come home.  On second thought, I'd rather
dance with the cows till you come home.
		-- Groucho Marx</description>
    </group>

    <group id="58">
      <name>name58</name>
      <description>(58) TIRED of calculating components of vectors?  Displacements along direction of
force getting you down?  Well, now there's help.  Try amazing "Dot-Product",
the fast, easy way many professionals have used for years and is now available
to YOU through this special offer.  Three out of five engineering consultants
recommend "Dot-Product" for their clients who use vector products.  Mr.
Gumbinowitz, mechanical engineer, in a hidden-camera interview...
	"Dot-Product really works!  Calculating Z-axis force components has
	never been easier."
Yes, you too can take advantage of the amazing properties of Dot-Product.  Use
it to calculate forces, velocities, displacements, and virtually any vector
components.  How much would you pay for it?  But wait, it also calculates the
work done in Joules, Ergs, and, yes, even BTU's.  Divide Dot-Product by the
magnitude of the vectors and it becomes an instant angle calculator!  Now, how
much would you pay?  All this can be yours for the low, low price of $19.95!!
But that's not all!  If you order before midnight, you'll also get "Famous
Numbers of Famous People" as a bonus gift, absolutely free!  Yes, you'll get
Avogadro's number, Planck's, Euler's, Boltzmann's, and many, many, more!!
Call 1-800-DOT-6000.  Operators are standing by.  That number again...
1-800-DOT-6000.  Supplies are limited, so act now.  This offer is not
available through stores and is void where prohibited by law.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="59">
      <name>name59</name>
      <description>(59) You have only to mumble a few words in church to get married
and few words in your sleep to get divorced.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="60">
      <name>name60</name>
      <description>(60) Time is fluid ... like a river with currents, eddies, backwash.
		-- Spock, "The City on the Edge of Forever", stardate 3134.0</description>
    </group>

    <group id="61">
      <name>name61</name>
      <description>(61) There's no easy quick way out, we're gonna have to live through our
whole lives, win, lose, or draw.
		-- Walt Kelly</description>
    </group>

    <group id="62">
      <name>name62</name>
      <description>(62) There was a young lady named Cager
Who, as the result of a wager,
	Consented to fart
	The entire oboe part
Of Mozart's quartet in F major.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="63">
      <name>name63</name>
      <description>(63) A manger went to his programmers and told them: "As regards to your
work hours: you are going to have to come in at nine in the morning and leave
at five in the afternoon."  At this, all of them became angry and several
resigned on the spot.
	So the manager said: "All right, in that case you may set your own
working hours, as long as you finish your projects on schedule."  The
programmers, now satisfied, began to come in a noon and work to the wee
hours of the morning.
		-- Geoffrey James, "The Tao of Programming"</description>
    </group>

    <group id="64">
      <name>name64</name>
      <description>(64) Prediction is very difficult, especially of the future.
		-- Niels Bohr</description>
    </group>

    <group id="65">
      <name>name65</name>
      <description>(65) Bubba, Jim Bob, and Leroy were fishing out on the lake last November,
and, when Bubba tipped his head back to empty the Jim Beam, he fell out of the
boat into the lake.  Jim Bob and Leroy pulled him back in, but as Bubba didn't
look too good, they started up the Evinrude and headed back to the pier.
	By the time they got there, Bubba was turning kind of blue, and his
teeth were chattering like all get out.  Jim Bob said, "Leroy, go run up to
the pickup and get Doc Pritchard on the CB, and ask him what we should do".
	Doc Pritchard, after hearing a description of the case, said "Now,
Leroy, listen closely.  Bubba is in great danger.  He has hy-po-thermia.  Now
what you need to do is get all them wet clothes off of Bubba, and take your
clothes off, and pile your clothes and jackets on top of him.  Then you all
get under that pile, and hug up to Bubba real close so that you warm him up.
You understand me Leroy?  You gotta warm Bubba up, or he'll die."
	Leroy and the Doc 10-4'ed each other, and Leroy came back to the
pier.  "Wh-Wh-What'd th-th-the d-d-doc s-s-say L-L-Leroy?", Bubba chattered.
	"Bubba, Doc says you're gonna die."</description>
    </group>

    <group id="66">
      <name>name66</name>
      <description>(66) A help wanted add for a photo journalist asked the rhetorical question:

If you found yourself in a situation where you could either save
a drowning man, or you could take a Pulitzer prize winning
photograph of him drowning, what shutter speed and setting would
you use?

		-- Paul Harvey</description>
    </group>

    <group id="67">
      <name>name67</name>
      <description>(67) Piping down the valleys wild,
Piping songs of pleasant glee,
On a cloud I saw a child,
And he laughing said to me:
"Pipe a song about a Lamb!"
So I piped with merry cheer.
"Piper, pipe that song again;"
So I piped: he wept to hear.
		-- William Blake, "Songs of Innocence"</description>
    </group>

    <group id="68">
      <name>name68</name>
      <description>(68) :fontology: /n./  [XEROX PARC] The body of knowledge dealing
   with the construction and use of new fonts (e.g., for window
   systems and typesetting software).  It has been said that fontology
   recapitulates file-ogeny.

   [Unfortunately, this reference to the embryological dictum that
   "Ontogeny recapitulates phylogeny" is not merely a joke.  On the
   Macintosh, for example, System 7 has to go through contortions to
   compensate for an earlier design error that created a whole
   different set of abstractions for fonts parallel to `files' and
   `folders' --ESR]</description>
    </group>

    <group id="69">
      <name>name69</name>
      <description>(69) Law of the Jungle:
	He who hesitates is lunch.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="70">
      <name>name70</name>
      <description>(70) "Lines that are parallel meet at Infinity!"
Euclid repeatedly, heatedly, urged.

Until he died, and so reached that vicinity:
in it he found that the damned things diverged.
		-- Piet Hein</description>
    </group>

    <group id="71">
      <name>name71</name>
      <description>(71) A general leading the State Department resembles a dragon commanding ducks.
		-- New York Times, Jan. 20, 1981</description>
    </group>

    <group id="72">
      <name>name72</name>
      <description>(72) The trouble with a kitten is that
When it grows up, it's always a cat
		-- Ogden Nash.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="73">
      <name>name73</name>
      <description>(73) "Anything else you wish to draw to my attention, Mr. Holmes ?"
	"The curious incident of the stable dog in the nightime."
	"But the dog did nothing in the nighttime."
	"That was the curious incident."
		-- A. Conan Doyle, "Silver Blaze"</description>
    </group>

    <group id="74">
      <name>name74</name>
      <description>(74) To err is human; to forgive is simply not our policy.
		-- MIT Assasination Club</description>
    </group>

    <group id="75">
      <name>name75</name>
      <description>(75) Experience is the worst teacher.  It always gives the test first and
the instruction afterward.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="76">
      <name>name76</name>
      <description>(76) A very intelligent turtle
Found programming UNIX a hurdle
	The system, you see,
	Ran as slow as did he,
And that's not saying much for the turtle.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="77">
      <name>name77</name>
      <description>(77) It seems like the less a statesman amounts to, the more he loves the
flag.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="78">
      <name>name78</name>
      <description>(78) Two heads are better than one.
		-- John Heywood</description>
    </group>

    <group id="79">
      <name>name79</name>
      <description>(79) :Commonwealth Hackish:: /n./  Hacker jargon as spoken in
   English outside the U.S., esp. in the British Commonwealth.  It
   is reported that Commonwealth speakers are more likely to pronounce
   truncations like `char' and `soc', etc., as spelled (/char/,
   /sok/), as opposed to American /keir/ and /sohsh/.  Dots in
   {newsgroup} names (especially two-component names) tend to be
   pronounced more often (so soc.wibble is /sok dot wib'l/ rather
   than /sohsh wib'l/).  The prefix {meta} may be pronounced
   /mee't*/; similarly, Greek letter beta is usually /bee't*/,
   zeta is usually /zee't*/, and so forth.  Preferred
   {metasyntactic variable}s include {blurgle}, `eek',
   `ook', `frodo', and `bilbo'; {wibble},
   `wobble', and in emergencies `wubble'; `flob',
   `banana', `tom', `dick', `harry',
   `wombat', `frog', {fish}, and so on and on (see
   {foo}, sense 4).

   Alternatives to verb doubling include suffixes `-o-rama',
   `frenzy' (as in feeding frenzy), and `city' (examples: "barf
   city!"  "hack-o-rama!"  "core dump frenzy!").  Finally, note
   that the American terms `parens', `brackets', and `braces' for (),
   [], and {} are uncommon; Commonwealth hackish prefers
   `brackets', `square brackets', and `curly brackets'.  Also, the
   use of `pling' for {bang} is common outside the United States.

   See also {attoparsec}, {calculator}, {chemist},
   {console jockey}, {fish}, {go-faster stripes},
   {grunge}, {hakspek}, {heavy metal}, {leaky heap},
   {lord high fixer}, {loose bytes}, {muddie}, {nadger},
   {noddy}, {psychedelicware}, {plingnet}, {raster
   blaster}, {RTBM}, {seggie}, {spod}, {sun lounge},
   {terminal junkie}, {tick-list features}, {weeble},
   {weasel}, {YABA}, and notes or definitions under {Bad
   Thing}, {barf}, {bogus}, {bum}, {chase pointers},
   {cosmic rays}, {crippleware}, {crunch}, {dodgy},
   {gonk}, {hamster}, {hardwarily}, {mess-dos},
   {nybble}, {proglet}, {root}, {SEX}, {tweak}, and
   {xyzzy}.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="80">
      <name>name80</name>
      <description>(80) "I think the sky is blue because it's a shift from black through purple
to blue, and it has to do with where the light is.  You know, the
farther we get into darkness, and there's a shifting of color of light
into the blueness, and I think as you go farther and farther away from
the reflected light we have from the sun or the light that's bouncing
off this earth, uh, the darker it gets ... I think if you look at the
color scale, you start at black, move it through purple, move it on
out, it's the shifting of color.  We mentioned before about the stars
singing, and that's one of the effects of the shifting of colors."
		-- Pat Robertson, The 700 Club</description>
    </group>

    <group id="81">
      <name>name81</name>
      <description>(81) :deprecated: /adj./  Said of a program or feature that is
   considered obsolescent and in the process of being phased out,
   usually in favor of a specified replacement.  Deprecated features
   can, unfortunately, linger on for many years.  This term appears
   with distressing frequency in standards documents when the
   committees writing the documents realize that large amounts of
   extant (and presumably happily working) code depend on the
   feature(s) that have passed out of favor.  See also {dusty
   deck}.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="82">
      <name>name82</name>
      <description>(82) A hypothetical paradox:
	What would happen in a battle between an Enterprise security team,
who always get killed soon after appearing, and a squad of Imperial
Stormtroopers, who can't hit the broad side of a planet?
		-- Tom Galloway</description>
    </group>

    <group id="83">
      <name>name83</name>
      <description>(83) Egotism is the anesthetic which numbs the pain of stupidity.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="84">
      <name>name84</name>
      <description>(84) There is a new anti-communist organization that advocates the use of
wooden toilet seats.

It's called the Birch John Society.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="85">
      <name>name85</name>
      <description>(85) We cannot do everything at once, but we can do something at once.
		-- Calvin Coolidge</description>
    </group>

    <group id="86">
      <name>name86</name>
      <description>(86) :Ada:: /n./  A {{Pascal}}-descended language that has been made
   mandatory for Department of Defense software projects by the
   Pentagon.  Hackers are nearly unanimous in observing that,
   technically, it is precisely what one might expect given that kind
   of endorsement by fiat; designed by committee, crockish, difficult
   to use, and overall a disastrous, multi-billion-dollar boondoggle
   (one common description is "The PL/I of the 1980s").  Hackers
   find Ada's exception-handling and inter-process communication
   features particularly hilarious.  Ada Lovelace (the daughter of
   Lord Byron who became the world's first programmer while
   cooperating with Charles Babbage on the design of his mechanical
   computing engines in the mid-1800s) would almost certainly blanch
   at the use to which her name has latterly been put; the kindest
   thing that has been said about it is that there is probably a good
   small language screaming to get out from inside its vast,
   {elephantine} bulk.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="87">
      <name>name87</name>
      <description>(87) Satire is tragedy plus time.
		-- Lenny Bruce</description>
    </group>

    <group id="88">
      <name>name88</name>
      <description>(88) If you didn't have most of your friends,
you wouldn't have most of your problems.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="89">
      <name>name89</name>
      <description>(89) Due to a shortage of devoted followers, the production of great leaders
has been discontinued.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="90">
      <name>name90</name>
      <description>(90) A diplomat is a person who can tell you to go to hell in such a way that you
actually look forward to the trip.
		-- Caskie Stinnett, "Out of the Red"</description>
    </group>

    <group id="91">
      <name>name91</name>
      <description>(91) What nonsense people talk about happy marriages!
A man can be happy with any woman so long as he doesn't love her.
		-- Wilde</description>
    </group>

    <group id="92">
      <name>name92</name>
      <description>(92) You can move the world with an idea, but you have to think of it first.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="93">
      <name>name93</name>
      <description>(93) A master was asked the question, "What is the Way?" by a curious monk.
	"It is right before your eyes," said the master.
	"Why do I not see it for myself?"
	"Because you are thinking of yourself."
	"What about you: do you see it?"
	"So long as you see double, saying `I don't', and `you do', and so
on, your eyes are clouded," said the master.
	"When there is neither `I' nor `You', can one see it?"
	"When there is neither `I' nor `You',
who is the one that wants to see it?"</description>
    </group>

    <group id="94">
      <name>name94</name>
      <description>(94) How doth the little crocodile
	Improve his shining tail,
And pour the waters of the Nile
	On every golden scale!

How cheerfully he seems to grin,
	How neatly spreads his claws,
And welcomes little fishes in,
	With gently smiling jaws!</description>
    </group>

    <group id="95">
      <name>name95</name>
      <description>(95) algorithm, n.:
	Trendy dance for hip programmers.</description>
    </group>

    <group id="96">
      <name>name96</name>
      <description>(96) It is November first 1940; in the famous sound stage of THE WIZARD OF OZ on
the MGM lot, a little man is lying face-up on the yellow brick road.  His
wide eyes stare upward into the blinding stage lights.  He is wearing a
kind of comic soldier's uniform with a yellow coat and puffy sleeves and
big fez-like blue and yellow hat with a feather on top.  His yellow hair
and beard are the phony straw color of Hollywood.  He could pass for some
kind of cute in the typical tinsel-town way if it wasn't for the knife
sticking out of his chest.  *Someone had murdered a Munchkin.*
		-- Stuart Kaminsky, "Murder on the Yellow Brick Road"</description>
    </group>

    <group id="97">
      <name>name97</name>
      <description>(97) This is not the age of pamphleteers. It is the age of the engineers.  The
spark-gap is mightier than the pen.  Democracy will not be salvaged by men
who talk fluently, debate forcefully and quote aptly.
		-- Lancelot Hogben, Science for the Citizen, 1938</description>
    </group>

    <group id="98">
      <name>name98</name>
      <description>(98) A programmer down in Moline
Said, I'm the match for any machine.
	My secret's aversion,
	To loops and recursion,
Just acres of in-line routine.
		-- W.J. Wilson</description>
    </group>

    <group id="99">
      <name>name99</name>
      <description>(99) You first parents of the human race... who ruined yourself for an apple,
what might you have done for a truffled turkey?
		-- Brillat-savarin, "Physiologie du Gout"</description>
    </group>

    <group id="100">
      <name>name100</name>
      <description>(100) :Macintrash: /mak'in-trash`/ /n./  The Apple Macintosh, as
   described by a hacker who doesn't appreciate being kept away from
   the *real computer* by the interface.  The term {maggotbox}
   has been reported in regular use in the Research Triangle area of
   North Carolina.  Compare {Macintoy}. See also {beige
   toaster}, {WIMP environment}, {point-and-drool interface},
   {drool-proof paper}, {user-friendly}.</description>
    </group>

</groups>

